chameleonjohn.com 2014-12-30

# Privacy Policy | Chameleon John

_Effective Date: February 7th, 2014_

This Privacy Statement ("Privacy Statement") explains how www.chameleonjohn.com ("Chameleon John", "Site"), a website owned and operated by Electrim Technologies Corporation, uses personal information and applies to all new users and affiliates who participate in, register on, or interact with, our site on or after the Effective Date. Please read this Privacy Statement carefully. If you do not agree to our practices, please do not register, subscribe, create an account, or otherwise interact with Electrim Technologies Corporation at www.chameleonjohn.com and all Site's Services we provide. 

Chameleon John may contain links to third-party websites, products and services. This privacy policy only applies to Chameleon John and our collection and use of your information. The linked websites, products and services of third parties, and their collection and use of your information, are governed by the privacy policies of such third parties. We encourage you to learn about the privacy practices of those third parties. 

**Information Collected During Registration**

When you create Chameleon John account, you provide some personal information, such as your name, surname, gender, country and email address. Some of this information, for example, your name and surname, could be listed publicly on our services, including comments, store reviews, shopping tips and on all your other activity within the Site. Exploring Chameleon John, searching for stores and using coupons do not require registration. 

**Automatically Collected Information**

When you use the Chameleon John or open one of our emails, we use technology (including cookies, IP addresses, unique device IDs, user IDs) to automatically collect non-personally identifiable information including: 

  * Coupon activity
  * Application activity (such as searches performed and features accessed)
  * Web browser type
  * The website that referred you to us
  * The web pages you viewed on Chameleon John
  * The advertisements you viewed and clicked on Chameleon John
  * The dates and times that you visited Chameleon John

**Additional Information**

You may provide us with additional information to make public, such as your shopping habits, location, photo, and everything else what is related to your online shopping. We may use your contact information to send you information about our services such as a newsletter, individual online stores activity you follow inside the Site. You may unsubscribe from these messages by following the instructions contained in the bottom of email. If you contact us, we may keep your message, email address and contact information to respond to your request. Providing the additional information described in this section is entirely optional. 

**Invite Friends**

If you choose to use our referral system to invite friends to Chameleon John, we will ask you for your friend email and your email address. We will use the information you provide to automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to join Chameleon John. We delete the email address shortly after fulfilling your request, do not share it with any third party and do not use for any other activities. 

**Cookies**

When you visit Chameleon John, we may send one or more cookies - a small text file containing a string of alphanumeric characters - to your computer. We use both session cookies and persistent cookies. A persistent cookie remains after you close your browser and may be used by your browser on subsequent visits to Chameleon John. These persistent cookies can be removed, but each web browser is a little different. Please review your browser's Help menu to learn how to modify your cookies setup. 

**Affilate Cookies**

Cookies sent to your computer by us, or our affiliates on our behalf, are governed by this privacy policy. The independent use of cookies by our affiliates is not covered by this privacy policy, as we do not have access or control over such cookies. Generally speaking, such cookies are used by affiliates to provide you with customized advertising. To learn more about cookies and how to manage them, please consult your browser's help menu. 

**Links**

Chameleon John will keep track of how you interact with links all over the site. We do this to make sure you will get your discounts and our rewards for your online shopping. 

**Information Sharing and Disclosure**

**Your Consent**

We may share or disclose your information with your consent, such as when you use a third party web client or application to access your Chameleon John account. 

**Service Providers**

We engage certain trusted third parties to perform functions and provide services to us. We may share your personal information with these third parties only for purposes to enrich your online shopping experience with us. 

**Law and Harm**

We may preserve or disclose your information if we believe that it is reasonably necessary to comply with a law, regulation or legal request; to protect the safety of any person; to address fraud, security or technical issues; or to protect Chameleon John rights or property. 

**Modifying Your Personal Information**

If you are a registered user of Chameleon John services, we provide you with tools to access or modify the personal information you provided to us and associated with your account. You can also ask to delete your Chameleon John account by contacting our support team. 

**Young Visitors Policy**

Chameleon John services are not directed to people under 16. If you become aware that your child has provided us with personal information without your consent, please contact us. We do not knowingly collect personal information from people under 16. If we become aware that a visitor under 16 has provided us with personal information, we take steps to remove such information and terminate the account. 

**Changes to this Policy**

We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time. The most current version of the policy will govern our use of your information and will always be at [www.chameleonjohn.com/privacy-policy](http://www.chameleonjohn.com/privacy-policy). If we make a change to this policy that, in our sole discretion, is material, we will always make a notice in the top of this page. By continuing to access or use our services after those changes become effective, you agree to be bound by the revised Privacy Policy.
